<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brew Lady - Adventures in home brewing</title>
    <link>http://brewlady.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brew Lady - Adventures in home brewing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brewlady.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertising Disclaimer</title>
      <link>http://brewlady.com/pages/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brewlady.com/pages/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>Affiliate Links When I mention equipment or products that I use on this website, I use Amazon affiliate links to earn a commission on any sales that take place from the link being used. Links to products that aren&amp;rsquo;t on the Amazon domain are not commissioned, and I include these to make sure anyone can recreate the processes that I describe.
Advertisements Advertisements are a means for me to generate revenue from this website and I cannot speak to the quality of the products being advertised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All-Grain Brew Day Guide</title>
      <link>http://brewlady.com/guides/1-brew_day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brewlady.com/guides/1-brew_day/</guid>
      <description>Introduction All-grain brewingBrewing using grains as the main ingredient, rather than extract.  seems intimidating, but actually isn&amp;rsquo;t as complex as one would think. Personally, I struggle with extract and never seem to get it all out of the container, so all-grain brewingBrewing using grains as the main ingredient, rather than extract.  agrees with me. The only additional equipment you need to go from extract brewingBrewing using malt extract syrup  to all-grain brewingBrewing using grains as the main ingredient, rather than extract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary of Terms</title>
      <link>http://brewlady.com/guides/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brewlady.com/guides/glossary/</guid>
      <description>A | B | C | D | E | F | G | H | I | J | K | L | M | N | O | P | Q | R | S | T | U | V | W | X | Y | Z
A Aroma Hops  These are added near the end of the boil, and typically are only boiled or 15 minutes or less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pilsner Brew Day - July 2019</title>
      <link>http://brewlady.com/blog/2019-07-13_pilsner_brew_day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brewlady.com/blog/2019-07-13_pilsner_brew_day/</guid>
      <description>Today is brew day, and I will be cooking the Brewer&amp;rsquo;s Pantry &amp;lsquo;Pilsners&amp;rsquo; kit. This is my first attempt at an all-grain brewBrewing using grains as the main ingredient, rather than extract. , and the only additional equipment that I had to purchase was the mash tunLarge insulated container used for steeping grains in hot water (see mash).  and some 1&amp;frasl;2 inch tubing! The jump from extract brewingBrewing using malt extract syrup  to all-grainBrewing using grains as the main ingredient, rather than extract.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>